

My Contact

prashul.shetty@gmail.com

\$\mathbb{C}\$ +91 976 991 0370

 C/103, Spring, Rajhans Seasons, Vasai (W), 401202

Hard Skill

- · Data mining and analysis
- Financial accounting
- Business valuation
- Proficient in Financial, Economic and Rating Databases

Soft Skill

- · Innovative Thinking
- · Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking
- Team Handling

Tools

- . Rating Database S&P, Moodys & Fitch
- Financial Database Bloomberg, Factset, Eikon, Factiva, Dealogic
- · Market Datbase Capital IQ, IBIS, Orbis
- · Excel, Macros, PPT, and Power BI

Achievements

- 2020 Silver Ovation winner for the gap analysis of database resulted in cost savings of GBP 2.6 million for the bank over 3 years
- 2012-2020 Managed five projects on process improvement

Education Background

- N.L. Dalmiya Institue of Management, Mumbal
 Masters in Financial Management
 Completed in 2015
- Patkar College, Mumbai University Bachelor of Management Studies, (Major in Finance), Mumbai Completed in 2006
- New English College, Mumbai Higher Secondary Completed in 2003
- Carmelite Convent English High School, Mumbai
 Senior Secondary
 Completed in 2001

Prashul Shetty

Market Research Consultant

About Me

Market Researcher with 12+years of experience in different organisations. Eager to learn and apply new ideas and agile way of working. Special interest in achieving the financial freedom and helping with retirement and general financial planning.

Professional Experience

Willis Towers Watson | Team Lead/Research Consultant (Markets and Client Insight Team)

2023 - Till Date

Key responsibilities:

- Providing market insights and secondary research support to corporate risk broking and advisory team, health and wealth benefits team and other key stake holders by profiling existing clients and prospective clients of the organizations.
- Reviewing company profiles of juniors, guiding and mentoring them on the research part
- Preparing industry reports/complex rapid research for different regions with trends, risks, sub segments, ESG and competitor analysis
- Co-ordinating with the stakeholders to scope their research requirement and provide with the timelines to adhere
- Bringing efficiencies in day to day operations with initiatives like automation and gap analysis

Natwest Group. | Lead Analyst/Research Consultant

2012 - 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Supporting Investment Bankers and Analysts in making Strategic business decision and building cases by providing Company Industry and Economic data through SWOT, PESTLE, Trends and Financial Analysis
- Preparing reports/Marketing Materials consist of Company Profiles, Info Packs, Newsletters and League Tables
- Consulting, Assigning and implement initiatives for process improvement and Mentoring/Training requirement for the team
- Providing comparative analysis of the Databases like Bloomberg, Elkon, Dealogic, S&P, Moody's, ESG etc for selecting and negotiating the database contracts on performance and price
- Ad-hoc projects delivery as per the need and requirement of the stakeholders like New Product Analysis or Competitor Analysis

Integreon Managed Solutions (India) Pvt. Ltd | Sr. Research Associate

2010 - 2012

Key responsibilities:

- · Working on Financial Databases to provide secondary research
- · Creating Company Profiles and Industry Research data
- . Worked on the Pilot Project for JP Morgan onsite for I year

TCS Eserve Ltd | Associate

2007 - 2010

Key responsibilities:

- Handling Pricing Maintenance and queries for Trade Finance Products of Citibank
- Preparing MIS reports for the respective Trade Departments
- Handling of the document control unit and project for process improvement